Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Events, 1870, 1917-2019; 25 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 11 manuscript boxes, one half manuscript box, 1 flat-file folder, 1 card box, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 28 boxes without container profiles.; 47 audiocassettes
  - Petrie Lecture, February 26, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - NYU in Albany Day, March 9, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - State Democratic Party Forum, March 16, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Onassis Convocation Technical Information, March 30, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Onassis Convocation, March 30, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hellenic Convocation and Dinner, April 1987 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_012 -- 7_4_014)
  - Spring Celebration, April 4, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee Meeting, April 16, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Postmaster General Dinner, Spring 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Very Special Arts Festival, May 8, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Third Elmer Holmes Bobst Award, May 19, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner Program, June 4, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dormitory and Information Center Dedication Ceremonies, June 14, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Service Awards, June 30, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Solicitation for Raffle Prizes, July 23, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - New Phonathon Center, August 26, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hayden Foundation Conference, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Attire Sale, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Jerome S. Coles Medal, Fall 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Recent Alumni Circle Line Trip, September 18, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - President's Reception at the Violet, September 21, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Fix Concert at Coles, September 26, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Latin American Conference, October 5, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - All-University Dinner Dance and Convocation, October 22, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3-7)
  - Farber / Hughes Dinner, November 10, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lee Hamilton Lecture / Dinner, November 16, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Kriser School of Dentistry Convocation, November 18, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24-25)
  - N.I.H. Conference, December 3, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wall Street Premiere, December 7, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Libraries and Librarians, December 15, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Libraries, December 15, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1987-1988 Alumni Lecture Series (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Awards / Awards Event Committees, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1987 Marnold Fellow (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Relations Event Ephemera, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Lecture Series, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - First Annual All-University Basketball Homecoming, January 21, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences Meeting, February 1988 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Palm Beach / Trustees Schedule, February 7, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Marnold Lecture, February 18, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture -- Tom Wicker, March 10, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14-15, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_017)
  - Nominating Committee of the Alumni Federation, March 30, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Washington Square Park Clean Up, April 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Health Fair / Presidential Forum, April 7, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, April 12, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Meritorious Service Awards, April 12, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner Package, April 13, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Heights Lounge / 170 Waverly, April 14, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Spring Celebration, April 30, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Belford-Thompson Lecture, May 4, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Creo Society, Inc., May 18, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, June 11, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Thomas S. Foley Lecture and Dinner, July 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Forum, August 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Michael Dukakis, Cuomo, et al, August 11, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - United Staff Association Strike, August 29, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Franois Mitterand Procession Guest List, September 28, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Franois Mitterand Convocation, September 28, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Franois Mitterand Convocation, September 28, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Mayor of Athens, September 29, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - French Revolution Bicentennial, October 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies -- Inaugural Lecture -- Vryonis, Georgakis, October 10, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_018)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, October 20, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Bobst Literary Awards Dinner, November 14, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Leonard Stern Events, Fall 1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Carter Hall, December 12, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dinner: Mr. And Mrs. Leonard N. Stern, December 13, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Kirball Center for Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli Marimo, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Federation Nominating Committee, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NYU Magazine, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "The Bayrd Still Trolley" Potential Project, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Robert W. Johnson Grant Press Conference, February 2, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Stern School of Business -- Lubin Memorial Guest Lecturer -- Allen E. Murray, February 15, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Bowsher Luncheon and Seminar, February 27, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner Package, March 22, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - National Education Forum, April 28, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - George Washington Arch 100th Anniversary -- Press Clippings, Promotional Flier, April 30, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Trustee Dinner, May 17, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - The Federation Annual Dinner, May 24, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - NYU Alumni College (WSUC and Heights), Summer 1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mayoral Debates (Channel 13), September 6, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Robert F. Wagner Press Conference, September 25, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_021)
  - TSOA/TOKYO Presidential Citations, September 26, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, September 27, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - H.E. George Vassilou, October 5, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - UAA Dinner, October 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Successful Aging Conference, November 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Battle for Columbia, November 1, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, November 8, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Sciences, November 9, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dedication, November 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_024)
  - Wagner Graduate School Dinner, November 16, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon in Honor of M. Schwarz, November 17, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - New World Salon Quartet, December 1989 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_022)
  - NYU Choral Arts Society, December 6, 1989 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_023)
  - Gift to Washington Square Park, Fall 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1, 8)
  - Alma Mater, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Coles Student Center -- Special Events Set-up, Memos, Floor Plans, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Resource Network Lunch, January 25, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_025)
  - Fernandez Reception, February 28, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Giulio Andriotti Convocation, March 8, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Luncheon in Honor of His Excellency Giulio Andreotti, Prime Minister of Italy, March 8, 1990 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_026 -- 7_4_027)
  - Rita Sssmuth Lecture and Dinner, March 19, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_028 -- 7_4_029)
  - Students' Black Tie Ball, March 24, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Violet Ball, March 24, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Fritz, John Honorary Degree, May 9, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, May 16, 1990 (Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_031)
  - President of Brazil, Spring 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Stern School of Business Building Groundbreaking, June 20, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_032 -- 7_4_033)
  - Bassists' Convention, June 27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Patriarch of Constantinople, July 17, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Federation: Keogh Award, September 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Prime Minister Toshiki Kaifu of Japan Convocation, September 28, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_034)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP) Centennial, October 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - President Carlos Salinas de Gortari of Mexico Convocation A and B, Address, October 1, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 2-3, Box 50, Folder 1, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_035)
  - Alumni Council Meeting -- Information Packet, October 17, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Music Therapy Clinic: School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP), October 18, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Greeks and the Sea, November 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture: Rupert Murdoch, November 8, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
  - Alumni Finance Forum, November 10, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, November 13, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - World AIDS Day, December 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bobst Awards, December 4, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Carter-de Menil Awards, December 10, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - NYU in Albany Day, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  - Alumni Relations Business Forum -- Promotional Material, Memos, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - College of Dentistry Alumni Events -- Promotional Material, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Distinguished Alumni, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ultra Violet Opening, January 1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Alumni: Florida Gathering, January 19, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Homecoming: Basketball, February 17, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Homecoming, February 17, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, February 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NYU in Albany Day, February 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 12-15)
  - Violet Ball, March 23, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Dean Oppenheim Farewell, April 11, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Hub N Apple Concert II, April 13, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Green Thumb '91, April 23, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Charles Haughey, PM of Ireland, May 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Council: Awards Commmittee, May 1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Council Meeting and Dinner, May 8, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ireland House -- Prime Minister of Ireland Speech, May 20, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_037)
  - Dental School 125th: PH Dinner, May 22, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Relations Weekend, June 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Boris Yeltsin Address, June 21, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_038)
  - Alumni Relations: NYU Picnic, September 14, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
  - Classroom Dedication, September 21, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Study Center Dedication -- L. Jay Olivia, September 20, 1991 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_039)
  - Hopkins-Pechar Golf and Tennis, October 13, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Federation Dinner, October 23, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Convocation for Vclav Havel, President of the Czech Republic -- Information, Guest List, October 27, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3-5, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_040)
  - President L. Jay Oliva Inauguration Events -- Images, Guest Lists, Planning Files, November 11-21, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 5-8, Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - Bobst Awards Dinner, December 4, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Goodman Chamber Choir, February 1992 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_041)
  - NYU in Albany Day, February 25, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
  - Giulio Andreotti Book Reception, March 10, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_042)
  - NYU Conference, April 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Village Improvement Day, April 21, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Park Tragedy, April 23, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Mayor Anatoly Sobchak Visit, May 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Windows Project, Spring 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, June 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - H.E. Albert Reynolds, Prime Minister of Ireland -- Luncheon and Visit, September 15, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_044 -- 7_4_045)
  - Second Annual NYU Picnic, October 3, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey Alumni Clubs Dinner, October 8, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Stern / Coles Volleyball Night, October 14, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Italian American Heritage Month Celebration, October 15, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Federation Awards Dinner, October 15, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - All University Dinner Dance, October 22, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Varsity Club Awards Dinner, October 28, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Federation Finance Forum, November 14, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade, November 26, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square News, Winter 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - University: New York University in New York City, Winter 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Conference: "De Benedetti" Visit, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The USA Up Close by Giulio Andreotti, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - NYU Cook Book, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Weehawken Athletic Complex Campaign -- Promotional Material, Memos, Press Clippings, 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 1992-1993 Regional Basketball Game Receptions, January 13, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, January 28, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NYU in Albany Day, February 23, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9, Box 20, Folder 1, Box 21, Folder 2)
  - University Senate Members Calendar of Selected Upcoming Events, March 11, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire Plaque, March 25, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - International Rectors' Conference, April 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Heights Centennial, April 17, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Stern M.E.C. Dedication, April 23, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Park Accident: 1st Anniversary, April 23, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Ireland House Dedication, April 26, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 1-3, Box 38, Folder 2, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_047 -- 7_4_048)
  - Kriser Annual Dinner -- Planning Memos, Guest Lists, April 29, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Federation Political Forum, May 4, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, May 12, 1993 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_049)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, June 1, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_052)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, June 3-5, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Annual NYU Alumni Cruise, June 6, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - NYU Tax Society 42nd Anniversary Dinner, June 16, 1993 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_053)
  - Shimon Peres Visit, September 28, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Westchester / Fairchild Counties Reception, October 6, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Varsity Club Awards Dinner, October 28, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Seventh All-University Dinner Dance, November 4, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Federation Finance Forum, November 20, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Main Building Lounges and Lecture Hall, Fall 1993 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Regional UAA Basketball Receptions, December 5, 1993 - February 20, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Chet Huntley Book Party, December 10, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Tax Society and Money Marketeers, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Finance and Business Club, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Honorary Degrees -- Correspondence, Planning Forms, Script, 1993, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
  - 1994 "NYU in Florida", February 16, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - NYU in Albany Day, March 1, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4-5, 11)
  - NYU in Albany Day, March 1, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Heyman Hall, March 14, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Cuomo / C.A.T. Reception, March 21, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - NYS Commission on National and Community Service, March 21, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - CAT / Cuomo Reception, March 24, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Shimkin Classrooms Naming, April 5, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Brown Plus Forty, April 13, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Silverstein Lounge Dedication, April 21, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - V.I.P. Day, April 27, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Kriser Annual Dinner -- Planning Memos, Guest Lists, April 28, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Higher Education Opportunity Program (HEOP) 25th Anniversary, April 29, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, June 1, 1994 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_054)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend -- Information Packet, June 3-5, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - NYU Picnic, September 7, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - School of Social Work Dedication, September 19, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 13, 30)
  - School of Social Work Dedication, September 19, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_055)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture: Shimon Peres, September 29, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 12, Box 22, Folder 15, Box 27, Folder 3, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_056)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, October 11, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Federation Awards Dinner, October 13, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - AmeriCorps Induction Ceremony -- Press Clippings, Schedule, Speech, Memos, October 14, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Dedication Ceremony for Fiorello H. LaGuardia Statue -- Promotional Material, Guest List, Press Clippings, Audio Recording, October 19, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 3, Box 27, Folder 2, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_057)
  - Varsity Club Dinner, October 20, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame, November 16, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Federation Finance Forum, November 19, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - All-University Holiday Sing -- Promotional Flier, December 5, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - School of Education -- English Madrigal Dinner -- Program, December 6, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - NYU Calendar, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Science and Math Ed. Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Council Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Senior Year Experience -- Committee Memos, Informational Material, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Student Senators Dinner, February 2, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - School of Social Work and Foundling Hospital Event, April 25, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1, 3)
  - Kriser Annual Dinner -- Planning Memos, Guest Lists, April 27, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Council Annual Dinner -- Program, June 7, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, June 8-11, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend -- Information Packet, June 8-11, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 9, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - NYU Staff Picnic -- Promotional Material, Memos, September 16, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Convocation -- Marching Letters, etc., October 12, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Fed: Varsity Club Dinner, October 20, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Academic Convocation: President Kim Young-sam -- Marching Letters, Invitation, General Information, October 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 1-6, Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Secretary Riley Visit, October 25, 1995 (Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_058)
  - Convocation and Reception -- Acceptance Lists, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Gallatin Convocation, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Gould Plaza -- Planter Plans, Memos, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Degree Convocation, June 10, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Event Fliers, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - All-University Orientation Guide, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 -- Promotional Material, Instructions / Script, Photographs, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6-8)
  - September 11th: Our University Remembers Event, Program, September 11, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - NYU 175th Anniversary Celebration Invitation, Memorabilia, November 7, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Honors and Awards Events, 2014, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 1, 3-4)
  - Welcome Day, 2016 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Inauguration of NYU President Andrew Hamilton, 2016 (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
  - A Celebration of the Life of NYU University Archivist Nancy Murphy Cricco, 2015 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Welcome Day Brochures, Dormitory Briefing Books, 2019 (Box Shared University Archives 088, Folder 5-6)
  - Welcome Day Flyer, 2019 (Box Shared University Archives 062, Folder 6)
  - Welcome Day T-Shirt, 2019 (Box Shared University Archives 062, Folder 7)
  - NYU / Night, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Instructions for Attaching NYU Emblems, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - International Dimensions at NYU, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Series II: Publications, 1956-2024; 15 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 3 flat boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 9 boxes without container profiles.; 5 audiocassettes
  This series contains printed items created for New York University events. Files in this series include programs, schedules, booklets, and promotional and marketing material dating from 1956 to 1995. Events include awards ceremonies, convocations, NYU anniversaries, and receptions for special guests and dignitaries. This series includes a large collection of Founders' Day event programs as well as audio recordings dating from 1956 to 1993. Planning files for many of the events in this series can be found in Series I.
  This series is arranged in groupings and chronologically within.
  - Founders' Day, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1957-1959 (Box 38, Folder 10-12)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1960-1969 (Box 38, Folder 13-22)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1970-1973 (Box 38, Folder 23-26)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 27-29)
  - Founders' Day -- Award Certificates, 1977-1981 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Founders' Day -- Notes, Concerns, 1978-1990 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1982-1986 (Box 38, Folder 31-35)
  - Founders' Day, April 23, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Founders' Day, April 24, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Founders' Day, April 16, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_020)
  - Founders' Day Program, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Founders' Day, April 22, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 7, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_030)
  - Founders' Day, April 21, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6, Box 53, Audiocassette 7_4_036)
  - Founders' Day, April 26, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_043)
  - Founders' Day, April 18, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3-4, Box 37, Folder 6, Box 54, Audiocassette 7_4_046)
  - Founders' Day Certificate (New Design), 2024 (Box Shared University Archives 157, Folder 1)
  - Founders' Day Blank Certificates, undated (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1984 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Student Handbooks and City Guides, 1979-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1, Box 55, Folder 2-4)
  - Convocation for Jehan El-Sadat Invitations, March 25, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Sesquicentennial -- NYU 150th Anniversary, October 13, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Sesquicentennial -- Mayor's Proclamation, October 13, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - NYU Calendar Book, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Calendar, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Convocation, October 11, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Third Annual Faculty Convocation, November 14, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Bobst Library 10th Anniversary, October 25, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Fourth Annual Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, November 10, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - King of Spain Convocation, November 2, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)